[{"answer": "You called me shmoppy. You're a shmoopy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You're a shmoopy", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You're a shmoopy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You're a shmoopy", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "All right, then. I'll see you later", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Bye shmoopy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Boy, I'm in the mood for a cheeseburger", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What soup place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hi shmoopy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You're a shmoopy", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Just like that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I just don't feel like it anymore", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Just like that", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And I cancelled plans to go to the movies with them tonight", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You know, we absolutely should", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You know, we absolutely should", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know. He can be so weird sometimes", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. What are you doing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You can't take this. This belongs to a friend of mine", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No. In what way", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't think my friend has ever thought he's better than anybody", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Happy? Why should I be happy", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "How can I tolerate any less from my customer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Por favor", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It was stupid of me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. I know. I", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Aw", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, hi my friend, my friend. You remember my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Ahh. Good for you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't know, honey. What do you want to get?  I want you to get anything you want...'cause I love you so much. I want you to be happy. Okay, sweetie", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh! Oh, I love it! I absolutely love it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "The K Man did it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'll tell ya where I got it. I got it from the guy you so callously refer to as the Soup Nazi", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What? Who's was it? Where'd you get it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Get out!", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Get out of my way, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Don't make me hurt you, my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well. Well", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Hey, my friend, my friend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Soup.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah. See ya", "qsentId": 46}]